{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449314348","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449314348"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449314722","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449314722"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449315206","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449315206"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449315549","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449315549"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449315953","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449315953"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449316427","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449316427"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449316650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449316650"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449319834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449319834"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449319867","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449319867"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449320581","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449320581"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449320973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449320973"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449321267","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449321267"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449321469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449321469"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449321662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449321662"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449321975","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449321975"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449322199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449322199"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449325394","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449325394"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449325797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449325797"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449328301","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449328301"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449328505","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449328504"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449328707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449328707"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449332138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449332138"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449335808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449335808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449336840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449336840"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449339474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449339474"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449339847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449339847"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449340331","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449340331"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449340674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449340673"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449341077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449341077"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449341550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449341550"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449341772","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449341772"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449344974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449344974"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449345007","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449345007"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449345720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449345720"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449346114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449346114"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449346407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449346407"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449346610","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449346610"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449346803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449346803"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449347116","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449347116"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449347339","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449347339"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449349995","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449349995"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449350048","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449350048"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 05ecac41-2bfe-4c17-af86-bf91d8aa7ed9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449360134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449360134"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449360667","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449360666"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449360890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449360890"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449361573","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449361573"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449362637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449362637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449363571","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449363571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449364374","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449364374"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449365198","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449365198"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449368992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449368992"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449369816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449369816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449370409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449370409"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449372936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449372936"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449374199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449374199"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWASAIDIA"," userResponse":" WALIWASAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449374983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449374983"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449375877","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449375877"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449376351","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449376351"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449377224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449377224"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" SHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449380539","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449380539"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449382053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449382053"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATAZWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATAZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449382506","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449382505"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449383169","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449383169"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449383371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449383371"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449383965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449383965"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449387368","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449387368"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449387830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449387830"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449388313","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449388313"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449389306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449389306"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449390220","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449390220"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449393102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449393102"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449393355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449393355"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449393527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449393527"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449394181","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449394181"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449395246","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449395246"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449396119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449396119"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEUMBWA"," userResponse":" WAMEUMBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449396442","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449396442"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449396975","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449396975"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449400232","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449400232"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449400885","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449400885"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANA"," userResponse":" KIJANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449401567","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449401567"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449402601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449402601"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449403044","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449403044"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449403727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449403727"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449404691","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449404691"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449404925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449404925"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449405598","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449405598"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANA"," userResponse":" MCHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449408686","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449408686"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449409229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449409229"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449410172","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449410172"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449410375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449410375"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449410808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449410808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449411232","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449411232"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449412565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449412565"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAZIDI"," userResponse":" IKAZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449415204","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449415204"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449416262","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449416262"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONYA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449417021","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449417021"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIENDE"," userResponse":" ASIENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449417818","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449417817"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUANI"," userResponse":" JUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449420762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449420762"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449422135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449422134"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUSIKIA"," userResponse":" HAKUSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449425612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449425611"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" ALIYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449425867","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449425866"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449426459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449426458"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449426901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449426900"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449427619","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449427618"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449428444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449428444"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" KALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449431688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449431688"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449431930","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449431929"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449432282","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449432282"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449433838","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449433837"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" WALIHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449435055","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449435055"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOONA"," userResponse":" WALIPOONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449435499","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449435498"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449435983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449435982"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449437259","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449437258"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" AKIYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449440735","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449440734"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAPANGA"," userResponse":" WAKAPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449441147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449441146"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449441881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449441880"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANI"," userResponse":" FULANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449444727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449444727"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHUKUA"," userResponse":" WALICHUKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449445319","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449445319"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449446640","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449446639"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOYEYUKA"," userResponse":" ILIYOYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449448115","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449448115"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATENGEZA"," userResponse":" WAKATENGEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449448669","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449448668"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449452091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449452091"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWEKA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449452635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449452635"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449453097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449453096"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449453549","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449453548"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449453810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449453810"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449454436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449454436"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449455182","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449455181"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449458221","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449458220"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449459607","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449459606"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" LILIPOCHOMOZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449460853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449460852"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449462930","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449462929"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPEPERUKA"," userResponse":" AKAPEPERUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449464127","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449464127"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449464481","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449464481"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449465357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449465356"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449467988","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449467986"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549449468092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549449468092"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450234627","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450234627"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 62213825-9b69-4d74-af1a-fad745c5955a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450253085","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450253085"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450259735","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450259734"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_8_5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450266387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450266387"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450273869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450273868"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450282883","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450282883"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450289106","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450289106"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450296595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450296594"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450305647","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450305646"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450311840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450311840"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450319265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450319265"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450328283","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450328283"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450334508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450334508"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_4_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450341133","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450341133"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_9_2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450348649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450348649"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_9_2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450357688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450357687"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_9_2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450363915","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450363914"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_2_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450370552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450370551"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450378024","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450378024"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450387070","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450387069"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450395659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450395659"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 488954f4-fd28-463b-985d-45db89611bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450525355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450525355"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_D_Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450531977","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450531977"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_S_H"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450538603","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450538603"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_O_L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450546043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450546042"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_O_L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450556448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450556447"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_O_L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450562646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450562646"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_L_CH"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450569235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450569235"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_I_S"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450576693","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450576693"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_I_S"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450587047","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450587047"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_I_S"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450593264","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450593264"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_L_A"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450599853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450599853"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_L_K"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450607295","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450607295"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_L_K"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450613937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450613937"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_B_H"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450621397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450621396"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_B_H"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450627996","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450627995"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_W_L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450634613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450634613"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_U_Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450642087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450642087"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_U_Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450652442","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450652442"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_U_Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450660868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450660868"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 20d39859-a37e-4776-8fac-73ed4cd0179d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_L_U_Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450670440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450670440"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450670990","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450670990"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450672491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450672491"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450673406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450673406"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450674138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450674137"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450674625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450674625"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450675428","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450675427"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450678441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450678441"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450678660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450678660"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450679144","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450679143"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450680050","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450680050"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450681807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450681807"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TULIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450682583","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450682582"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450683125","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450683125"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450684539","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450684538"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGETUGAWIA"," userResponse":" ANGETUGAWIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450685379","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450685379"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450685944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450685944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450689485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450689484"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450690830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450690830"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKANGU"," userResponse":" KAKANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450692127","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450692126"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450693790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450693789"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450696697","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450696696"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" ALIYALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450697529","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450697529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450697809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450697808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450698765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450698764"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450699870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450699870"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450700135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450700133"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450703132","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450703131"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450703389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450703389"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450703882","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450703882"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450704609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450704609"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450706030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450706029"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450708029","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450708028"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULILIA"," userResponse":" TULILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450709520","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450709520"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISEMA"," userResponse":" TUKISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450711007","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450711006"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450711192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450711191"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450712328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450712328"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" MTUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450713366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450713365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450713617","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450713617"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450714637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450714637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOYO"," userResponse":" MCHOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450717516","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450717516"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450719264","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450719264"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450720602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450720601"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450722082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450722081"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450722794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450722794"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450724326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450724325"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450725192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450725190"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450726834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450726832"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450728200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450728200"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMELIWA"," userResponse":" YAMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450731116","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450731116"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450731346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450731346"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450731816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450731816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450732563","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450732562"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450734324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450734323"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" TULIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450735090","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450735090"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450735752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450735751"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450736524","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450736524"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450737381","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450737380"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450740951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450740951"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TULMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450741653","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450741652"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450742830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450742829"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450744296","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450744295"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," userResponse":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450744942","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450744941"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450748396","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450748395"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450749257","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450749255"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450750421","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450750420"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450751880","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450751879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450752704","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450752704"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450754643","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450754643"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," userResponse":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450757845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450757844"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450759161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450759161"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450760267","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450760266"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450761545","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450761545"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450762307","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450762307"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450765343","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450765342"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450766914","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450766912"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450767835","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450767833"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450768102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450768102"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450768947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450768946"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450769091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450769090"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450769784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450769784"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450771303","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450771303"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAUMWA"," userResponse":" NAUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450771624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450771623"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450772346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450772346"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450776056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450776055"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450776974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450776974"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450777661","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450777660"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450778683","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450778683"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450779488","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450779487"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450780254","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450780253"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450781185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450781185"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450782303","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450782303"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450782772","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450782771"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450783622","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450783622"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450784983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450784982"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGECHAPWA"," userResponse":" ANGECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450785194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450785194"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450785701","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450785700"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450789229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450789228"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450790592","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450790592"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPOPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450791260","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450791259"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFUU"," userResponse":" NAFUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450792852","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450792852"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450794154","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450794153"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUOMBA"," userResponse":" ALITUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450795383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450795383"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450798001","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450798000"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450798083","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450798083"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" 4af1fea7-dede-4eeb-9de3-baf019324161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450811368","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450811367"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_R-F-L"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450815809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450815809"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_CH-M-L"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450819105","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450819104"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-F-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450822531","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450822531"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-G-O"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450827243","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450827243"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-U-CH"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450830679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450830678"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_N-I-L"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450836148","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450836148"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_N-I-L"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450839193","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450839193"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-L-H"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450842660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450842660"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_O-T-L"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450848329","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450848328"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_O-T-L"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450855581","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450855580"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_O-T-L"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450862645","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450862645"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-J-H"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450866997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450866997"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-J-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450872773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450872772"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_133457"," gameId":" c424bd51-d17f-40c0-9abe-8aed09da4993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-J-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}